Vaibhav Sharma

Building and deploying Deep Learning based Computer Vision projects for a fast paced healthcare startup, have applied knowledge in NLP and Speech processing and develop React Native apps to bring ML to mobile devices.

458-E Professor Colony Yamunanagar,Haryana 9992575847 Vaibhavpandit21@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Advenio Tecnosys, Research Engineer

November 2019 - PRESENT

>Optic Disk detection using Faster-RCNN & Classification

Localizing and extracting optic disc from Retina images using **Faster-RCNN** in Keras and Tensorflow.building a pipeline RCNN+CNN to classify extracted Optic Disc and deploying the prototype on AWS EC2 using a flask server.

>Generating Synthetic data for Augmentation using GANs

Generating synthetic fundus images using **BAGAN** for augmenting data to remove class imbalance in **Keras**.

>Multi-Label Disease Classification from Fundus images

Boosted CNN classifier ensemble using Fast-Al for Prototyping and Pytorch for development ,Interpretability and deploying the model on **AWS Lambda** and in browser via **ONNX**.

Kandarp Advertising Solutions, Deep Learning Engineer

May 2019 - November 2019

>Age and Face predictor for Advertising Billboards

Built a Wide Resnet regressor and classifier model to predict the age and gender of people looking at an advertising billboard.Built pipeline for retraining the model on the live data stream from edge devices.

>Facebook Marketing Data Analytics

Predicting user engagement with an advertisement on Facebook, using **LightGBM** and tabular Pytorch NN with **sklearn skorch**.

PUBLICATIONS

> Published <u>DeepCap: A Deep Learning Technique to caption black and</u> <u>white images</u> in Confluence 2020

EDUCATION

Jaypee Institute of Information Technology, Noida, B.Tech, Computer Science Engineering

2015 - 2019.

Core Competencies

Pytorch,OpenCV,Tensor flow,Keras,Dlib,NumPy, CuPy, MySQL, Spacy, TorchText, scikit learn, MongoDB, AWS[Sagemaker,S3,EC2 Lambda], Flask,Django, React-Native,Firebase.

LANGUAGES

Python, Javascript, R, C++

SOCIAL & DEV

Blog & Portfolio: https://Vaibhavpandit.s pace

Github:

https://github.com/Vaib hav21pandit

LinkedIn https://linkedin.com/Va ibhavpandit21